

CONTACT

+1-778-215-2483

Email

ncmoseley@gmail.com

Site

youfoundnate.com

SKILL

CSS	JavaScript
Node.js	React/Redux
Wordpress	PHP

FOLLOW MF

GITHUB

github.com/NCMoseley

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/ncmoseley

Instagram

instagram.com/moseleync

NATHAN MOSELEY

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Transitioning swiftly from a successful professional role in a different industry to tech is a testimony to my passion and drive. I am now pursuing my dream of building apps, and I have developed a deep passion for all things code. I look forward to becoming part of a team that builds the latest in user experiences. I am extremely dedicated to my craft, and am deeply enjoying the process of intense learning and being creative again.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sept 2018 – Nov 2018 | React Native Developer Get in the Loop | Kelowna British Columbia

 Working directly with the project manager allowed me to learn best practices in a very streamlined and efficient way. During this contract I mastered the fundamentals of application software design and continued to exercise my understanding of the Full Stack development industry. Our app is finished and soon to be available in the App store.

Nov 2016 – Oct 2017 | Technical MWD Training Consultant, North America Applied Physics Systems | Sunnyvale, California

Traveled over the US and Canada to well sites, training Field Engineers
to use Applied Physics MWD technology. I had to set the standard for
organization, professionalism, and technical proficiency. This
technology is heavily computer focused, and a deep understanding of
software, networks, and battery systems is required.

Jan 2014 – March 2015 | MWD Manager ROP Services Ltd/ Matrrix Technology Services Ltd | Calgary, AB

> Responsible for management and coordination of 20 field engineers and associated equipment for the technical side of directional drilling operations throughout Northern Canada, I would also ensure the project documentation was accurate and fully communicated to the customers, well planning staff, and senior management. I learned time efficiency and excellent leadership skills.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Professional Developer Power Engineering 4th Class Red Academy | Vancouver BC, March, 2018 SAIT | Calgary, AB September 2013